I'm pretty sure Israel used to have that land.
I'm pretty sure you're wrong.
They withdrew from 2005 from the land, but controlled the air.
No, they don't give it to them.
They control the air, the sea space, the borders,
the population registry.
They controlled what went in and out.
It was a prison, an open-air prison.
That's not giving them freedom.
But don't they have a border with Egypt and then
the Mediterranean Sea?
Yes, and the Israelis and Egyptians work together
because Donald Trump and Joe Biden and Barack Obama.
Yes, they're funded by the United States.
Did you know that Muslim countries do bad things, too?
No, I know that they do bad things.
Okay, then, so we're in agreement.
All right, pause.
You've been voted out.
Please return to your seat.
Nice to meet you.